-Tell him. -Tell him.
-告訴他嘛… -對,就告訴他嘛
-Shut up. -Tell me what?
-閉嘴. -告訴我什麼?
You won't look at him.
你看你,連正眼看他都不肯
I could use another reason why women won't look at me.
下回女人不看我時我有了新借口
All right. All right. Last night,I had a dream...
好吧,好吧,昨晚我夢見
...that you and I were
我和你
Doing it on this table.
在這桌上做愛
Excellent dream score.
夢中得分
Why would you dream that?
你怎會有這種夢?
More importantly...
最重要的是
...was I any good?
我棒嗎?
Well,you were pretty damn good.
簡直是棒極了
Interesting. In my dreams, I'm surprisingly inadequate.
真有意思,在我夢中我力不從心
Last night,you seemed to know your way around the table.
昨晚你在桌上表現神了
I love it when we share.
真高興能與你們分享
You okay?
你沒事吧?
I can't believe you two had sex in her dream.
我不敢相信你會在她夢中做愛
Sorry,it was a one-time thing.
抱歉,我只有一次
I was very drunk,and it was someone else's subconscious.
我醉得不省人事,而且這是某人的潛意志
The One With The lck Factor
六人行 第1季 第22集 倒人胃口的約會
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 榮譽出品 河馬根據網絡字幕微調製作
Hello,Rachel.
好呀,瑞秋
Get off.
起來
Ooh,give me. Can you see me operating a drill press?
給我,你們能想像操作鑽床的我嗎?
I don't know. What are you wearing?
不知道,你當時穿什麼?
Why would you want to?
不知道,你為何想操作鑽床?
For short-term work. Till I get back my massage clients.
只是暫時的工作,直到我找回部份的按摩客戶
Pirates again?
又是海盜?
No. Nothing like that.
沒那回事
I'm just such a dummy.
我是個大笨蛋
I taught a "Massage Yourself at Home" workshop. And they are.
我教他們「自己在家動手作按摩」 結果他們就在家裡作
Hey,Chan,she could work for you.
嗨,錢德,她可以為你工作
Thanks,Joey. That's a good idea.
謝了,喬伊,這是個好主意
I could. I could do it. What is it?
我可以,是什麼工作?
My secretary's gonna be out. She's having one of her boobs reduced.
我秘書這幾周無法來上班 她去動消乳手術
It's a whole big boob story.
一言難盡的波霸故事
-I could be a secretary. -I don't know if it'd be your thing...
-我可以當個秘書 -我不知你是否是這塊料
... because it involves being normal for a large portion of the day.
-因為這份工作得要表現「正常」? -白天要盡量正常
I could do that.
我能辦到
-What's that? -My new beeper.
-那是什麼? -我的新BP機
Why does a paleontologist need a beeper?
古生物學家要那玩意兒幹嘛?
Is it for dinosaur emergencies? Help. They're still extinct.
恐龍緊急事件?救命啊, 快來,他們還是絕種了
It's for when Carol goes into labor.
不,是為卡蘿生產買的
All she has to do is dial 55-JlMBO.
她隨時可以連絡到我, 她只需撥個號碼55-JIMB0
A cool number and a possible name for the kid.
這號碼真酷還能當孩子的名字
-See you later. -Off to see young Ethan?
-各位回頭見了 -去見伊森小子?
Thank you.
謝謝
How young is young Ethan? Young?
伊森到底有多小?很小?
He's our age.
年紀和我們差不多
When we were....
當我們還是…
-He's a senior in college. -College?
-他是大學四年級學生. -大學?
Rob that cradle.
這就是起源
He's smart and mature and grown-up.
他聰明,穩重和成熟
Mature and grown-up,he's a big boy.
穩重和成熟,他是個大男孩
This man-child has no problem with how old you are?
這位小朋友不在乎你的年紀?
No,of course not. It's not even an issue...
當然不在乎
... because I said I was 22.
因為我告訴他我22歲
-You what? -What?
-你什麼? -什麼?
-Oh,I can't pass for 22? -Well,maybe 25,26.
-我不像22歲? -25,26還說得過去
-I am 26. -There you go.
-我今年26. -那就對拉
Can you hear that?
聽見沒?
That'll stop when you pick up the phone.
拿起電話後就會停
-Oh,I'm on. -Okay.
-我來. -好吧
Mr. Bing's office.
賓先生辦公室
-Sorry,he's in a meeting. -I'm not in a meeting.
-抱歉,他正在開會. -我沒在開會我在…
Will he know what this is in reference to?
他知道這件事嗎?
And he has your number?
他有你的號碼?
I'll see that he gets the message. Bye-bye.
好,我會轉告他的,再見
Ross says hi.
羅斯打來問候的
This is so fun. What do we do now?
真好玩.現在做什麼?
Well,now I actually have to get to work.
現在我得開始工作了
"Most likely."
「沒錯」(Magicball顯示)
Okay,I'm gonna be out there.
我出去一下
All right. Bye-bye.
好的,拜拜
Bye-bye.
拜拜
-Yes? -What you doing?
你在幹嗎?
Okay,windows are clean. Candles are lit.
窗戶擦好了,蠟燭點上了
BeIt's too tight. Gotta change.
皮帶太緊,我得去換一條
Did I turn the fish? Nope,because I made lasagna.
魚翻過了沒? 沒,因為我做的是千層面
-Am I out of control? -Just a touch.
-我是否已走火人魔? -一點點
I don't understand. You've been dating this guy since...
我不懂.你們從他期中考…
... his midterms.
…開始約會
Why,all of a sudden, are you so...?
為什麼,突然間你…
-What? -Could tonight be the night?
-我怎麼了? -就在今夜?
I don't know. He's a great guy...
我不知道,他是個好男孩
...and I love being with him. But,you know...
我喜歡和他在一起,但是,很難說
...things happen when they happen. You don't plan these things.
事情會發生就是會發生,這種事無法事先計劃好
-So,did you shave your legs? -Yeah.
-腿毛刮了沒? -刮了
Would you let it go? It was just a dream.
羅斯,你就別再折磨自己了 這只是一場夢
It doesn't mean
不代表…
This is it. It's baby time!
時候到了,寶寶要出世了
All right,relax. Just relax. Be cool.
放輕鬆…冷靜點
Yeah,hi. I was just beeped.
有人呼我
No,Andre is not here. Third time today.
不,安卓不在這兒,今天已是第三次了
Yes,I am sure.
對,我確定
I do not perform those kind of services.
沒錯,我不做那種服務
Services?
服務?
Oh,services.
哦,服務?
Yeah,you want 55-JUMBO.
對,你要打的是55-JUMB0
That's right.
沒錯
That's right. JUMBO with a "U," sir.
沒錯,有U的JUMB0
You don't want me.
不,先生,相信我你不會想要我的
Judging by his number, I'd be a huge disappointment.
從他的號碼看來,你看到我會大失所望
Alrighty,bye-bye.
好吧,再見了
How was the first day?
第一天上班如何?
Excellent. Everyone was so,so nice.
太棒了,每個人都很棒
It pays to know the man who wears my shoes.
瞧,認識穿我鞋子的人是有代價的
Me.
我
-I didn't tell anyone I knew you. -Why?
-不,我沒告訴任何人我認識你. -為什麼?
Well,because,you know.
因為,你知道的
They don't like you.
他們並不喜歡你
-What? -I thought you knew.
-什麼? -我以為你早知道
-Who doesn't like me? -Everyone.
-誰不喜歡我? -每個人
Except for....
除了…
No. Everyone.
不,每個人
-What are you talking about? -Don't feel bad.
-你說什麼? -別難過
They used to like you a lot.
他們過去都很喜歡你
But you got promoted,and now you're Mr. Boss Man. Mr. Big.
自從你升職後,他們感覺你是上司
Mr. Bing. Boss Man Bing.
大人物,大老闆
-I can't believe it. -Yeah. They even do you.
-我簡直無法相信. -他們甚至還模仿你
They "do" me?
模仿我?
You know,like,okay:
對,比如這樣
"Could that report be any later?"
報告要「何時」才能交來?
-I don't sound like that. -Yeah,you do.
-我沒有那樣. -你有的
"The hills are alive with the sound...
這山谷迴盪著真善美的
...of music."
音樂
"My scone. My scone."
我的烤餅,「我」的烤餅!
I don't sound like that. That is so not true.
我沒那樣說話,這「不」是真的
That is so not That is so not
不是這樣,不是這樣
That Oh,shut up.
這不…閉嘴
-Did not. -Up until I was 9...
-不會吧. -告訴你,我到九歲時
... I thought "gunpoint" was a place where crimes happened.
還以為槍口就是犯罪現場
-How's that possible? -It's always on the news.
-怎麼會. -新聞老是報導犯罪事件
"A man is being held up at Gunpoint."
某人在槍口下
"Tourists are terrorized at Gunpoint."
驚慌的觀光客在槍口下
And I kept thinking, "Why do people continue to go there?"
我一直在想為何人總是要那兒去
I should go.
我該走了
-Unless -What?
-除非. -什麼?
Unless you wanna stay over.
除非你要在這兒過夜
I mean,I'm going to. So....
我反正要在這裡過夜…不如
Yeah,I'd really like that.
我也很想
Before we get into any staying-over stuff...
在我們考慮留宿的事宜之前
...there's something you should know.
我有些事情必須告訴你
Is this,like, "I have an early class tomorrow"...
這個就像,明天一早有課?
...or "I'm secretly married to a goat"?
還是你與山羊秘密結婚了
Well,it's somewhere in between.
在這兩者之間
You see,in a strictly technical sense,of course,I'm not....
就嚴格的技術上而言,當然,我還沒
Well,I mean,I haven't ever....
我是說,我還沒有
Ethan?
伊森
Are you a virgin?
你是個處男?
If that's what you kids are calling it these days,then...
如果你們這些孩子,現在這樣稱呼的話
...yes,I am.
對,我是個處男
I mean,you're just such a good kisser I would never have known.
我是說,你確實是個很會接吻的傢伙,我沒想到
Well,I've excelled at every level I've been to,I just....
我在每一個級別都是是優秀,我只是
I just haven't been to that particular one yet.
我一直在等待夢中情人出現
I've kind of been waiting for the right person.
我一直在等待適合的人
-Really? -Yeah.
-真的? -真的
You do know I was talking about you,right?
你知道我是在指你吧?
Wow.
喔
You keep saying that.
你一直喔個不停
You know,you read about it. You see it in the movies.
書報雜誌,電影上不斷出現
Even when you practice it at home, man,oh,man...
甚至在家裡練習
...it is nothing like that.
這感覺實在沒得此
Listen,listen.
聽著
You told me something that was really difficult for you.
你說你有些困擾
And I figure if you can be honest,then I can too.
如果你能坦白,我想我也能
Don't tell me I did it wrong.
別告訴我是我做錯了
Nothing wrong about that.
不,那件事你沒做錯
Here goes.
我說了
I'm not 22.
我不是22歲
I'm 25...
我是25歲
...and 1 3 months.
又13個月
But I figure that shouldn't change anything.
我猜我們之間不會有任何改變
What does it matter how old we are? Basically,I'm nuts about you.
年齡根本就不是距離, 而且,我完全被你迷倒了
I knew after the first time we kissed. You didn't mention the Tic Tac.
我們第一次接吻就知道了,你沒有提到「Tic Tac」
I just thought you were naturally minty.
我只是覺得你有一種自然的薄荷香
Listen...
聽著
...as long as we're telling stuff...
在你坦承之際
... I have another one for you.
我也有話要說
I'm a little younger than I said.
我比你所知的年紀還小
-You're not a senior? -Oh,I'm a senior...
-你不是四年級? -我是四年級
...in high school.
高中
What we did was wrong.
我們錯了
I just had sex with someone who wasn't alive during the bicentennial.
我竟和一個在建國兩百年國慶 都還沒出生的男人做愛
I just had sex.
我剛做愛了
Ethan,focus. How could you not tell me?
伊森,注意聽,你為何不早告訴我
-You never said your age. -It's different.
-你也沒告訴我你實際的年齡. -那不一樣
My lie didn't make one of us a felon in 48 states.
我的謊言不會使我們成為罪犯
-What were you thinking? -I was too busy falling
-你到底在想什麼? -我只是忙於
-Don't say it. -ln love with you.
-不要說. -愛上你
-Really? -Sorry.
-真的? -對不起
Well,fall out of it.
好吧,從裡面出來吧
You shouldn't be here. It's a school night.
走吧,你不該來這兒的,你該在學校過夜的
Oh,God.
天啊
I'm like those women that you see...
我就像是那種…
...with shiny guys named Chad.
專門勾引小帥哥的女人
I'm Joan Collins.
我成了瓊考琳絲
Who?
誰?
Andre should be there in about 45 minutes.
好,安卓再45分鐘就會到
Yes,sir,the kimonos are extra.
是的,長官,和服很特別
Alrighty. Bye-bye.
好吧,再見
It's just easier that way.
這樣省事多了
-You told me about the last dream. -No. Forget it.
-快,你已告訴我昨晚的夢 -不,死了這條心的
Why not? Was I doing something particularly saucy?
為什麼?難道是夢中的我對你過於粗魯
All right. Fine.
好吧
You were not the only one there.
不僅僅你在場
Joey was there too.
喬伊也在場
All right.
好的
Was there...
那
...anybody else there?
還有其他人嗎?
You sure? Nobody...
真的?沒有…
... handing out mints or anything?
…蠢蠢欲動的傢伙?
No,it was just the three of us.
沒有,只有我們三個
So was it you and Chandler...
是你跟錢德之後
...then you and me, or you,me and Chandler?
再跟我,還是我們三個同時?
-You know what? -What?
-你知道嗎? -什麼?
There were times...
有幾次…
...when it wasn't even me.
…甚至沒有我
That is so sweet,you guys.
真好,夥計們
Mon,Ethan called again.
摩尼卡,伊森又來電了
-What? -Ethan called again.
-什麼? -伊森又來電了
-You're not seeing him anymore? -No.
-你不想再見到他了? -不想
Sometimes,things don't work out.
對,有些事是無法勉強的
This has nothing to do with him needing a note to get out of gym?
這跟他需要假條才能離開學校無關?
I did not say anything. I swear.
我什麼都沒說,我發誓
-He stopped by. -Next time you talk to him...
-他只是順路過來. -下回見到他時
...could you ask him which one the strongest Power Ranger is?
能問閃電俠中最強的是誰?
Oh,my life is just so amusing. Can we drop it now?
我的生活簡直是太多采多姿了 可以換個話題嗎?
Sorry.
對不起
"It's morphin'time."
嗎啡時間到了
-Stegosaurus. -Tyrannosaurus.
-暴龍! -劍龍!
I gotta go.
我得走了
Head rush.
哇哦,腦充血
One more,and then I have to go.
再一回我就得走了
Cool.
酷
Where you going?
你要上哪兒去?
A birthday party with some work people.
我要和同事去參加生日會
Work people? Nobody told me.
同事?沒人跟我說?
I know. That's part of the whole...
我知道,他們中的一部分…
...them-not-liking-you extravaganza.
…不希望你大駕光臨
A month ago, these people were my friends.
一個月前他們是我朋友
I'm in charge, but I'm not a different person.
當上主管並不代表我會變
Then come,hang out. Let them see what a great guy you still are.
那麼說你今晚該來,和他們多相處 讓他們知道你還是個大好人
-You think I should? -I really do.
-你真的認為我該去? -對,你該去
But could we not go together?
我們能不一起去嗎
I don't wanna be the geek who invited the boss.
我不想成為邀請上司的傢伙
-Hey,you okay? -Yeah.
-嗨,你怎麼樣? -是的
-This can't be easy for him either. -I know.
-這對他來說也並不容易. -我知道
This may take some time for him to get over it...
也許他需要一些時間來度過這個
... but,then at four, Muppet Babies is on.
但是,四點閃電俠就要開始了
Go deep. Deep. Deep.
更深點,深點,深點
Sorry,Shelly.
對不起,雪莉
See,with the fun?
看到沒有,很開心?
Last night was great.
昨晚真是太棒了
The karaoke thing? Tracy and I doing "Ebony and lvory."
卡拉0K,我和崔西合唱了首「烏木與象牙」
You were great. But they still made fun of you.
你表現得很好,大家仍然取笑你
-What? -Now you're Mr. Caring Boss.
-什麼? -你現在成了「管家婆」上司
Mr. I'm-one-of-you Boss.
「我要你」上司
Mr. I-wanna-be-your-buddy Boss Man Bing.
「稱兄道弟」上司
Then I don't get it.
我更迷糊了
You know what? I think you just gotta face it.
錢德,你得面對現實
You're the guy in the big office.
你像個坐在大辦室裡的人一樣
You're the one that hires and fires them.
有權錄取他們,也有權開除他們
-They say you're a great boss. -They do?
-他們說你是個好上司. -是嗎?
But they're not your friends anymore.
但是他們不再是你的朋友
-I just want -But you can't.
-我只是想. -你不能
But I just want
我只是想
Are you gonna?
不是要去…
Carol and I have a new system. If she punches in 9-1 -1...
卡蘿和我有了新系統,如果打911
...she's having a baby. Otherwise,I just ignore it.
就代表她將生產,否則我就根本不理會
What about Andre?
安卓呢?
He got a call from our cousin,Nathan.
早上他接到我表弟納森的電話
Frankly,it was a little more than I needed to know.
老實說我知道太多內幕了
That was gonna be my opener.
那也是我的開場白
Have you guys seen those new hand dryers in the bathroom?
你們看過浴室裡的新吹風機沒?
-I thought that was just a rumor. -True story.
-我以為那只是謠傳.-千真萬確
Look,I gotta tell you something.
我得和你談談
I'm not 1 7. I said that so you'd think I was vulnerable.
我不是17歲,我這樣說 你才會認為我可愛惹人憐
I'm actually 30. I have a wife and a job. I'm your congressman.
其實我今年30,我有老婆和工作,我是國會議員
This is ridiculous. We're great together.
摩妮卡,這太荒謬了,我們在一起很開心
We can talk,make each other laugh,and the sex....
我們聊天說笑做愛
I have no frame of reference, but I thought that was great.
我雖然經驗不多,但一切是那麼美
-lt was. -Then what's the problem?
-的確是. -那麼問題出在哪兒?
Ethan,it's....
伊森
It's icky.
經不起考驗的
"lcky"?
「lcky」? 經不起考驗?
You're actually gonna throw this away because it's "icky"?
因為如此你就想放棄?
This isn't easy for me either. I wish things were different.
我是不得已的,我希望情形不是這樣
If you were older or I was younger...
如果你年長幾歲,我年輕幾歲
...or we lived in biblical times...
或是我們生活在聖經時代
-... I could really -No,don't say it.
-我就可以… -不要說
Love you.
愛你
-Are your hands still wet? -Moist.
-你的手還沒干? -還是濕的
Let's dry them again.
那就再去烘一次
Or,like,"Could these margaritas be any stronger?"
這些萄葡酒能再烈一點嗎?
Hey,Chandler.
錢德
Hello,Mr. Bing.
賓先生
Loved your Stevie Wonder last night.
我愛你昨晚的史提夫汪達
Thanks. About the weekly numbers,I'm gonna need them on my desk by 9:00.
謝謝.有關周數字的事 九點「之」前請送到我辦公室來
-Sure. -No problem.
-好的. -沒問題
You have to give them something.
總得給他們些話題嘛
That was Gerston,Santos,and who's the other guy?
剛剛是格斯頓,山托斯 留鬍子的那個叫什麼?
-Petrie. -Petrie. Right,okay.
-派崔. -派崔,對
Well,some people are gonna be working...
這週末有得有人
...this weekend.
…加班了
Oh,that's nice.
真好
Ross.
羅斯
I'm here.
我在這裡
You are?
你在?
We were just....
我們在.
What?
什麼?
-Great. Now I'm having a baby. -What?
-這下可好,我有寶寶了 -什麼?
I'm having a baby. I'm having a
我有寶寶了.我有一個
-The phone,the phone. -I don't have the phone.
-電話,電話 -電話在哪兒?
I'm hurt.
我受傷了
Let's go. Come on,people. Woman in labor.
摩妮卡,快走各位快點,她要生了
-Look what I got going. -Save it for the cab.
-羅斯,看這是什麼 -留著付計程車吧
We're going to a hospital.
你在幹什麼?我們要去醫院
I can't look nice? There are doctors there.
我不能漂亮一點嗎?那兒或許有醫生
-Joey,get out of the fridge. -All right.
-喬,別翻冰箱了 -好吧
-What is that? -For the ride.
-那是幹嗎的? -路上吃的
-Like in a cab -Save it.
-比如坐車的時候 -留著吧
-Hating this. -Monica,come on. Let's go.
-真討厭 -摩妮卡,快
Baby coming.
寶寶就要出世了
I can't believe I'm gonna be an aunt.
我真不敢相信,我快當姑姑了
-I'll have a nephew. -That's nice. Get out.
-我快有侄子了 -真感人,走吧
All right,I'm going. I'm going.
好的,我來啦,我來啦
Here we go. Come on.
走吧,趕緊